Search for:  

    [

](https://www.closetsbydesign.com/)

Follow us:

Call Closet by Design [Let's Get Started](https://www.closetsbydesign.com/ScheduleRequests/)

Privacy Policy
==============

[Home](https://www.closetsbydesign.com/) > Privacy Policy

Closets by Design respects the privacy of our customers, partners and suppliers of products or services and clients. The purpose of this Privacy Statement is to provide you with information concerning how we collect personal information; how we use, handle and disclose collected information; and choices you may have about the ways we collect and use that information. Our goal in handling personal information provided to us is to comply with applicable data protection and privacy laws and to offer our customers and other users of this website notice, choice and consent regarding communications for direct marketing purposes, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement with regard to personal information. “Personal information” means information that identifies you personally, either alone or in combination with other information available to us.

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.closetsbydesign.com This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website and in other communications with the company, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:

* What information we collect;
* With whom it is shared;
* How it can be corrected;
* How it is secured;
* How policy changes will be communicated; and
* How to address concerns over misuse of personal data.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing** We may collect personal information from you when you request information about a product or service, purchase a product or service, or otherwise elect to participate in an activity. If you contact us directly, such as through customer service, we may request information so we can respond to your question or comment and/or validate your identity. We may also collect information sent to us through your web browser. The information we collect may include, but is not limited to, your name, e-mail address, IP address, billing and/or shipping address, phone number, payment account information, and other information about you submitted to verify who you are or to prevent fraud. If you call our customer service, we may collect personal information you knowingly and voluntarily provide through your contact with our customer service representatives.

We are the sole owners of the information we collect from you on this site and in your other communications with the company, including at the time of a sale in order to complete your transaction and deliver products and services. We only have access to and collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you such as by phone or on the Consultation Scheduler Page. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as is necessary to fulfill your request for information or for our own marketing purposes (e.g., to ship an order, or to inform you about our promotions).

By using and entering information on this site, you are providing your express written consent to contact you using any contact information you provide to the company through this website or otherwise. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email or telephone in the future to tell you about specials, our products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. If you decide you no longer want to receive promotional messages or other communications from us, you may withdraw your consent to receive such communications by following any unsubscribe link in our emails or by contacting us.

We may in the future collect information that is typically not personally identifiable through the use of web technologies, including without limitation “session cookies,” and “persistent cookies.” As the Internet evolves, we may implement and use different types of technologies for this purpose. Web technologies may be placed on this site directly by us or by third party providers, and we or third party providers may place web technologies on behalf of the partner whose branding appears on this website or its service providers and allow that partner to utilize the data collected. This information will be used to enhance your use and experience with this website, for marketing analysis, for targeted and display advertising, and for quality improvement purposes. We may collect your IP address through web technologies.

Session Cookies. A “session cookie” is a temporary cookie that expires when you close your browser. A session cookie assigns a randomly-generated, unique identification number to your computer when you access this website. Assigning your computer a number facilitates the proper functioning of the features of our website by permitting us to maintain a persistent “state” for your session, such as maintaining the contents of your shopping cart during checkout.

Persistent Cookies. Unlike a session cookie, a “persistent cookie” does not expire when you close your browser. It stays on your computer until the expiration date set in the cookie (for example, at the end of a calendar month) or until you delete it. Persistent cookies can be used to “tag” your computer so that the next time you visit (or someone using your computer visits), our server will recognize you, not by name, but by the “tag” on your computer. This will enable us to provide you with a personalized experience even if we do not know who you are. It will also allow us to collect more accurate information about the ways people use this website, for example, how people use this website on their first visit and how often they return.  
**Your Access to and Control Over Information** You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number provided below:

* See what data we have about you, if any.
* Change/correct any data we have about you.
* Have us delete any data we have about you.
* See how we have shared your information
* Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security** We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees and our third-party business partners who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, to contact you for billing, customer service, or promotional purposes) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Notification of Changes** We may occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect, among other things, changes in applicable laws, rules or regulations, changes in our data collection practices, and/or changes to our business or services. Changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective 30 days after posting. We will post an updated version of this Privacy Policy on this website with a revised effective date, to let you know that we updated the Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy may also be supplemented or amended from time to time by additional “Privacy Notices” posted or appearing on this website or otherwise provided to you. Such Privacy Notices will provide supplemental information on how we collect and handle information specific to where that Privacy Notice appears, and are intended to be read together with this Privacy Policy.

**Children’s Privacy**

This website and our goods and services are not directed at or targeted to children. If you have not reached the age of majority or are not able to enter into legally binding agreements in your country, you may not use this website unless supervised by an adult. Our goal is to comply with applicable laws and regulations relating to collection and use of information from children as such term is defined by applicable laws. If you believe that we have received information from a child or other person protected under such laws, please notify us immediately by mail addressed to Closets by Design, Chief Operating Officer, Attn: Privacy, 3850 Capitol Ave, Whittier, CA, 90601, USA or by email at [cbdclientissues@closetsbydesign.com](mailto:cbdclientissues@closetsbydesign.com), and we will take reasonable steps to remove that information from our databases.

**Other Provisions as Required by Law** Numerous other provisions and/or practices may be required as a result of laws, international treaties, or industry practices. It is up to you to determine what additional practices must be followed and/or what additional disclosures are required. Please take special notice of the California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA), which is frequently amended and now includes a disclosure requirement for “Do Not Track” signals.

**Copyright Disclaimer**

Closets by Design, Everyday Collection, Classic Collection, Regency Collection and Infinity Office Systems, Everyday II, Classic II, Regency ll, Silver ll, designwall, designfloor, Traxtile, Flextile and designbed, are registered trademarks of Closets by Design, Inc. All featured photos are the property of Closets by Design, Inc. and may not be reproduced or used in any way without the written consent of Closets by Design, Inc.

**How to Contact Us**  
If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding Your Privacy Rights or this Privacy Policy, or have privacy-related questions not answered online, you may contact us by any of the following means:

* By Phone: You may contact us by phone at [(800) 500-9210](tel:+18005009210).
* By Email: You may contact us by e-mail at [cbdclientissues@closetsbydesign.com](mailto:cbdclientissues@closetsbydesign.com).

Please specify “Privacy Question” in the subject line to help us to expedite our review of your e-mail. You may write to us in your own language.

NEED TO KNOW MORE
-----------------

Join our email list
-------------------

Closets By Design

[

](https://www.closetsbydesign.com/)

##### Our Company

##### Connect With Us

© 2024 All Rights Reserved. | Closets by Design®, Inc.

Thank you for your interest in a career opportunity with Closets by Design. To find open position in your area. please enter your ZIP or Postal Code
